Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 4: Railroad Scenes, undated, 1876-1997
      - FDD's Lionel Train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3765)
      - FDD's Lionel Train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3766)
      - FDD's Lionel Train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3767)
      - Grove Beach, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3768)
      - Arch bridge, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3769)
      - Newport Carnival, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3770)
      - Main Street, Leominister, Massachusetts, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3771)
      - Naumkeag Street Railway car at Salem Willows, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3772)
      - Runaway Track, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3773)
      - Track views, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3774)
      - Unidentified four wheel street car, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3775)
      - 10 bench open car, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3776)
      - Street car on street, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3777)
      - Open car in Boston, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3778)
      - Street cars on street, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3779)
      - Snow covered cars, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3780)
      - Shelbourne Falls and Colerain Street Railway, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3781)
      - Trolley work train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3782)
      - Open car on street, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3783)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Nipmuc Park, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3784)
      - Bay State Railway, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3785)
      - View from fireman's cab window (Boston & Maine Railroad), undated (Box 37:, Folder 3786)
      - West Portal, Hoosac Tunnel, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3787)
      - West Portal, Hoosac Tunnel during construction, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3788)
      - Bridges at Millville, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3789)
      - Bridges at Millville, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3790)
      - New York & New England, Providence & Worcester bridges after flood, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3791)
      - Central New England crossing New York Central, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3792)
      - East Portal, Hoosac Tunnel, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3793)
      - East Portal, Hoosac Tunnel, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3794)
      - "East Wind" at Portland, Maine, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3795)
      - Freight house, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3796)
      - Shepaug Branch tunnel, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3797)
      - Bridgeport track views, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3798)
      - Track view, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3799)
      - Track view, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3800)
      - Car 29 on street, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3801)
      - Track view, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3802)
      - Merchants Bridge terminal, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3803)
      - Portsmouth, Rhode Island, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3804)
      - Hell Gate Bridge, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3805)
      - Flood Gate, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3806)
      - Central city switchback, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3807)
      - Bedford Street, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3808)
      - Waiting for the train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3809)
      - Merrimack Square, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3810)
      - Crossing trains, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3811)
      - Train ride, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3812)
      - Street car, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3813)
      - Airline Limited, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3814)
      - Saybrook Junction, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3815)
      - Employees, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3816)
      - Nashua, Massachusetts, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3817)
      - Milepost, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3818)
      - Engine house, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3819)
      - Southbridge local, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3820)
      - Track views, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3821)
      - Central Pacific Railroad engines, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3822)
      - Railway tracks, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3823)
      - Railway tracks, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3824)
      - Railway light signal, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3825)
      - Worcester Cemetery in Danbury, Connecticut, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3826)
      - Car on line, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3827)
      - Car on line, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3828)
      - Rail lines in rural neighborhood, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3829)
      - Oncoming train at Nantasket, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3830)
      - MBTA notice, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3831)
      - Covered bridge, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3832)
      - Trestle bridge, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3833)
      - Train in storm, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3834)
      - Boston & Albany carbarn, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3835)
      - Post office, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3836)
      - House near lines, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3837)
      - Power station, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3838)
      - Abandoned station, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3839)
      - Old station, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3840)
      - Town along rails, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3841)
      - Building community, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3842)
      - Whittenton Tower O-351, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3843)
      - Train at station, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3844)
      - Chatham railroad museum, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3845)
      - Chatham railroad museum, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3846)
      - Family standing next to train, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3847)
      - Woonsocket Junction, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3848)
      - Hotel at Summit, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3849)
      - Engineers in front of car, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3850)
      - Rail ride, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3851)
      - Holliston carbarn, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3852)
      - Train approaches station, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3853)
      - Preparing locomotives, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3854)
      - Loading coal, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3855)
      - View of top of locomotive boilers, undated (Box 37:, Folder 3856)
      - View of New River Gorge, 1946 (Box 37:, Folder 3857)
      - Lincoln Square, Milford, Massachusetts, 1906 (Box 37:, Folder 3858)
      - New Haven Railroad train, 1952 (Box 37:, Folder 3859)
      - Lowell Avenue bridge, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3860)
      - Bridges and tracks, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3861)
      - Supply house, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3862)
      - Woodstack, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3863)
      - Auburndale, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3864)
      - Motorman and conductor, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3865)
      - Boothby's Turnout, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3866)
      - Engine off turntable possibly at factory, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3867)
      - Carbarn, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3868)
      - Open trolley cars, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3869)
      - New Haven Street Railways employees, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3870)
      - Street car on street, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3871)
      - Open car fleet, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3872)
      - Street car on street, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3873)
      - Nantasket Beach, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3874)
      - Car "off the iron", undated (Box 38:, Folder 3875)
      - Line construction, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3876)
      - Tunnel entrance, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3877)
      - Truck open car, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3878)
      - Bridge at Quincy Point, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3879)
      - Bay State Street Railway, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3880)
      - Electric car terminus, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3881)
      - Car at Woburn, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3882)
      - Carbarn, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3883)
      - Main Street, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3884)
      - Cemetery Monument, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3885)
      - Nelson Blount's train, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3886)
      - Steam hoists, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3887)
      - Norfolk & Western on street, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3888)
      - Holliston center, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3889)
      - Electric car, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3890)
      - 1940s excursion, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3891)
      - Wellesley Square, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3892)
      - West Newbury horse car, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3893)
      - Street car on street, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3894)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Street Railway, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3895)
      - Carbarns, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3896)
      - Marlboro, Massachusetts, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3897)
      - Framingham Center, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3898)
      - Carbarn, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3899)
      - Open Norfolk Western Street car, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3900)
      - Pierce Square, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3901)
      - Framingham Center, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3902)
      - Motorman on Wrentham, Massachusetts, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3903)
      - Essex Street, Salem, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3904)
      - Unidentified scene, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 3905)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Non-railroad Scenes, undated, 1876-1997
      - "City of Hartford", 1876 (Box 38:, Folder 3906)
      - Hand fire engine "Reserve", undated (Box 38:, Folder 3907)
      - Muster Day with "Torrent", 1901 (Box 38:, Folder 3908)
      - "Mount Washington", 1907 (Box 38:, Folder 3909)
      - "Martha's Vineyard", 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 3910)
      - Steam Roller, 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 3911)
      - "Quebec", 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 3912)
      - "City of Bangor", 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 3913)
      - "Canada", 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 3914)
      - Baptist church, West Medway, circa 1910 (Box 38:, Folder 3915)
      - "Restless", 1910 (Box 38:, Folder 3916)
      - "New Hampshire", 1912 (Box 38:, Folder 3917)
      - Men around locomotive, builders photo, 1912 (Box 38:, Folder 3918)
      - Horsedrawn fire engine, hose 2, 1913 (Box 38:, Folder 3919)
      - "Dartmouth", 1914 (Box 38:, Folder 3920)
      - "Uncle Sam", 1919 (Box 38:, Folder 3921)
      - Power house, 1924 (Box 38:, Folder 3922)
      - U.S. Corps of Engineering, 1934 (Box 38:, Folder 3923)
      - U.S. Corps of Engineering, 1934 (Box 38:, Folder 3924)
      - U.S. Army Maintenance Shop, 1935 (Box 38:, Folder 3925)
      - Norwood Freight office, 1939 (Box 38:, Folder 3926)
      - Tugboat, 1948 (Box 38:, Folder 3927)
      - Airplane, circa 1949 (Box 38:, Folder 3928)
      - Airplane, BT13, circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3929)
      - Airplane, API "Stinson", circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3930)
      - Airplane, PT19, circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3931)
      - Airplane, PT19, circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3932)
      - Airplane, PT19, circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3933)
      - Airplane, "Taylorcraft", circa 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3934)
      - Fisherman's Wharf, 1950 (Box 38:, Folder 3935)
      - "Cote D'Azur", 1954 (Box 38:, Folder 3936)
      - Stone bridge, 1955 (Box 38:, Folder 3937)
      - Stone bridge, 1955 (Box 38:, Folder 3938)
      - Fire engine, 1958 (Box 38:, Folder 3939)
      - Hand fire engine, "Bay State", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3940)
      - Hand fire engine, "Bay State", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3941)
      - Hand fire engine, "Bay State", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3942)
      - Hand fire engine, "Hancock", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3943)
      - Hand fire engine, "Hydrant", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3944)
      - Hand fire engine, "Hydrant", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3945)
      - Hand fire engine, "Niagara", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3946)
      - Hand fire engine, "Tiger", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3947)
      - Hand fire engine, "Tiger", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3948)
      - Hand fire engine, "Torrent", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3949)
      - Hand fire engine, "Torrent", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3950)
      - Hand fire engine, "Eureka", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3951)
      - Hand fire engine, "Union", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3952)
      - Fire engine 4, Dover, Massachusetts, 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3953)
      - Fire engine, Forge Village, Massachusetts, 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3954)
      - Newport Harbor, 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3955)
      - "Provincetown", 1963 (Box 38:, Folder 3956)
      - "Newport" with Sheila and Kevin, 1964 (Box 38:, Folder 3957)
      - "Newport", 1964 (Box 38:, Folder 3958)
      - "Jamestown", 1964 (Box 38:, Folder 3959)
      - Old fire engine, 1965 (Box 38:, Folder 3960)
      - Steam Roller, 1966 (Box 38:, Folder 3961)
      - Steam Roller, undated (Box 38:, Folder 3962)
      - The Flumes, 1966 (Box 39:, Folder 3963)
      - The Flumes, 1966 (Box 39:, Folder 3964)
      - "Prudence II", 1967 (Box 39:, Folder 3965)
      - "Prudence II", 1967 (Box 39:, Folder 3966)
      - "Island Queen", 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 3967)
      - Underpass at Bellingham, Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 3968)
      - Rail Derrick, 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 3969)
      - "Martha's Vineyard", 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 3970)
      - Rock tunnel, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 3971)
      - Family where FDD's father and section gang worked 80 years prior, 1970 (Box 39:, Folder 3972)
      - Family where FDD's father and section gang worked 80 years prior, 1970 (Box 39:, Folder 3973)
      - Steam Roller, 1970 (Box 39:, Folder 3974)
      - R ton Roller, 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3975)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3976)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3977)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3978)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3979)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3980)
      - "Mount Washington", 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3981)
      - "Sophie C" mail boat, 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3982)
      - "Sophie C" mail boat, 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 3983)
      - "Hollister III", 1973 (Box 39:, Folder 3984)
      - "Cumberland," Rocky Hill, Connecticut, 1973 (Box 39:, Folder 3985)
      - Engine 6, Medway depot, 1974 (Box 39:, Folder 3986)
      - Greyhound scene cruiser, 1974 (Box 39:, Folder 3987)
      - Logan Airport, 1980 (Box 39:, Folder 3988)
      - Logan Airport, 1980 (Box 39:, Folder 3989)
      - Logan Airport, 1980 (Box 39:, Folder 3990)
      - Bridge at Glen and Jackson, New Hampshire, 1983 (Box 39:, Folder 3991)
      - Steam tractor, "Eclipse", 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3992)
      - Steam tractor, "Eclipse", 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3993)
      - Steam tractor, "Eclipse", 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3994)
      - Steam tractor, "Eclipse", 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3995)
      - Steam Roller, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3996)
      - Steam Roller, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3997)
      - Steam Roller, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3998)
      - Steam Roller, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 3999)
      - Steam Tractor, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4000)
      - Steam Tractor, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4001)
      - Steam Tractor, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4002)
      - Steam Tractor, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4003)
      - Steam Rollers, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4004)
      - Steam Roller CN 14191, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4005)
      - Steam Rollers, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4006)
      - Steam Rollers, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4007)
      - Steam Roller, 1988 (Box 39:, Folder 4008)
      - Steam Roller, 1989 (Box 39:, Folder 4009)
      - Steam Roller, 1989 (Box 39:, Folder 4010)
      - House, 1994 (Box 39:, Folder 4011)
      - FDD at Pondville Cemetery where father's gravel pit was in 1912-1915, circa 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4012)
      - Model T Ford Truck, 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4013)
      - Rumley "Oil Pull" Kerosene Tractor, 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4014)
      - Rumley "Oil Pull" Kerosene Tractor, 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4015)
      - Rumley "Oil Pull" Kerosene Tractor, 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4016)
      - Model steamboat, New Hampshire, 1997 (Box 39:, Folder 4017)
      - Model of "Portland", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4018)
      - Model of "Portland", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4019)
      - Model of "Portland", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4020)
      - Steamboat, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4021)
      - Fall River Steamboats, "Providence", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4022)
      - Fall River Steamboats, "Pilgrim", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4023)
      - Bath car ferry, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4024)
      - Bath car ferry, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4025)
      - Bath car ferry, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4026)
      - Bath car ferry, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4027)
      - "Rosedale", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4028)
      - "Betty Alden", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4029)
      - Steamer, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4030)
      - "Noddle Island", Boston 19, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4031)
      - "Nantucket", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4032)
      - "Armenia White", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4033)
      - Steamboat Landing, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4034)
      - "Newtown", Boston, Revere Beach & Lynn, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4035)
      - "Gay Head", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4036)
      - Unidentified tin type, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4037)
      - Steam Roller, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4038)
      - Steam Engine, "Eclipse", undated (Box 39:, Folder 4039)
      - Blimp above docks, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4040)
      - Site of Wrentham depot, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4041)
      - Dorothy, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4042)
      - Ticket office at fair, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4043)
      - Road before rail lines, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4044)
      - Profile photos, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4045)
      - View of marina, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4046)
      - Logging, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4047)
      - House, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4048)
      - House, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4049)
      - House, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4050)
      - Foliage, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4051)
      - Foliage, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4052)
      - Ducks on pond, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4053)
      - Farm, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4054)
      - Milepost B107, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4055)
      - Equipment, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4056)
      - House, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4057)
      - Caves, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4058)
      - Milepost WRI 36, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4059)
      - Horse, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4060)
      - Horse, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4061)
      - Work men at front of locomotive, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4062)
      - Work men at front of locomotive, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4063)
      - Horsedrawn fire engine, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4064)
      - Moveable steam traction engine for powering farm instruments, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2893)
  - Subseries B: 5x7 Flexible Negatives
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations (Box 40)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Engines (Box 40-41)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Cars (Box 41)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Railroad scenes (Box 41)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Non-railroad scenes (Box 41)
  - Subseries C: 4x5 Flexible negatives
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations (Box 42-48)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Engines (Box 48-55)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Cars (Box 55-56)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Railroad scenes (Box 57-59)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Non-railroad scenes (Box 59-60)
  - Subseries D: 5x7 Glass plate negatives
    - Sub-subseries 1: Engines (Box 61-63)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Railroad scenes (Box 63)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Non-railroad scenes (Box 63)
  - Subseries E: 4x5 Glass Plate negatives
    - Sub-subseries 1: Engines (Box 64-72)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Cars (Box 72)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Railroad scenes (Box 72)
  - Oversized prints and glass plate negatives (Box 73)